Hello welcome back!
In this segment we're going to be discussing how to make the client comfortable on the massage table.
So in this case we're working with a massage table, other individuals if they're in chair or in a bed, you'll deal with that as it presents itself to you.
So Molinia do you care to demonstrate with me?
I'm going to first have you sit up, great!
So when the individual gets on the table, first we have them sit on the side.
Can you swing your legs around?
There you go!
So they first get on the table like this and then we have them swing their legs onto the table, great!
Then, slowly lower yourself supporting her back and her head.
There we go, are you comfortable?
I am, great!
Can you lift your knees for me please?
Do you have any aches or pains?
A little on the hip.
On the hip?
Have you had a massage before?
No.
No, okay great!
Is there any part of you body that you would like special attention paid to?
A lot of stress right now, so I think just whatever that will help me relax.
Great, we can do that.
So after we find out what the needs are of our client and make sure your client is comfortable, then we're set to move on to the next segment.